<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Band Database</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>

    <string-array name="bands">
        <item>The Beatles</item>
        <item>Nirvana</item>
        <item>U2</item>
        <item>Linkin Park</item>
        <item>ABBA</item>
        <item>AC/DC</item>
        <item>Aerosmith</item>
        <item>The Allman Brothers Band</item>
        <item> Amadou and Mariam</item>
        <item>The Andrews Sisters</item>
        <item>The Animals</item>
        <item>Arcade Fire</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="descriptions">
        <item>An English rock band that formed in Liverpool in 1960.</item>
        <item>An American rock band that formed in Washington in 1987.</item>
        <item>An Irish rock band from Dublin that formed in 1976.</item>
        <item>Linkin Park is an American rock band from Agoura Hills, California.</item>
        <item>ABBA, Swedish Europop group that was among the most commercially successful groups in the history of popular music. </item>
        <item>AC/DC, Australian heavy metal band whose theatrical high-energy shows placed them among the most popular stadium performers of the 1980s.</item>
        <item>Aerosmith, American heavy metal band. One of the biggest arena-rock attractions of the late 1970s, Aerosmith became even more popular with its career revival in the mid-1980s.</item>
        <item>the Allman Brothers Band, American rock band whose bluesy, jam-oriented sound helped spark the Southern rock movement of the 1970s and set the stage for several generations of roots-oriented improvisational rock bands. </item>
        <item>Amadou and Mariam, Malian musical duo who achieved global success by combining West African influences with rhythm and blues.</item>
        <item>the Andrews Sisters, singing trio, one of the most popular American musical acts of the 1940s.</item>
        <item>the Animals, five-piece rock group from northeastern England whose driving sound influenced Bob Dylan’s decision, in 1965, to begin working with musicians playing electric instruments.</item>
        <item>Arcade Fire, Canadian alternative rock group that surged to international popularity in the early 21st century.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="date">
        <item>Date: 1960 – 1970</item>
        <item>Date: 1987 – 1994</item>
        <item>Date: 1976 - present</item>
        <item>Date: 1996 – present</item>
        <item>Date: 1969 – 1982</item>
        <item>Date: 1973 – 2016</item>
        <item>Date: 1970 - present</item>
        <item>Date: 1969 – 2014</item>
        <item>Date: 1986 – 2017</item>
        <item>Date: 1935 – 1948</item>
        <item>Date: 1964 – 1994</item>
        <item>Date: 2003 - present</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>